# Kristin Brumfield

Sacramento, Ca 95831 Phone: 559-909-3762

Email: brummy.k@gmail.com

LinkedIn: <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/kristin-brumfield-74a565178/">https://www.linkedin.com/in/kristin-brumfield-74a565178/</a>

GitHub: <a href="https://github.com/kbrummy">https://github.com/kbrummy</a>

Portfolio: <a href="https://kbrummy.github.io/UpdatedPortfolio/">https://kbrummy.github.io/UpdatedPortfolio/</a>

#### Summary

As a Front End Web Developer, I am striving to create functional and beautiful websites to my clients. I received my Full Stack Developer certification through UC Davis, and worked on many projects, both solo and in groups. My ability to work with a team and my attention to detail and design helped make the websites I worked on efficient and accessible. My hope is to carry over all the skills and knowledge I have learned in my time at UC Davis and apply that to a new career in the web development world.

#### **Technical Skills**

Languages: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, JQuery, NodeJS, Express, MongoDB.

## **Projects**

# Insta-Date | https://github.com/brianpraseuth/Group-Project-1-Insta-Date | https://brianpraseuth.github.io/Group-Project-1-Insta-Date/

Insta-date is a website that can be used to generate a random meal recipe, drink recipe, and play music for the ideal date night.

My responsibility on the project was finding the right API's to use, and to help code the page CSS.

In this project, we used HTML, CSS, JavaScript, JQuery, and Materialize.

# Experience

#### Sacramento Natural Foods Co-Op, 916-455-2667 Helper Clerk, December 2019 to current

Duties: Greeting and welcoming customers, loading customer purchases into bags with efficiency and care, general janitorial duties of the Front End, store grounds, and parking garage. Making sure supplies are stocked at the Front End. Providing product and store knowledge for customers when asked. Maintaining customer safety while cleaning various glass or liquid spills.

Sacramento Pipeworks: Climbing and Fitness, 916-341-0100 Customer Service Lead, May 2012 to June 2019

Duties: Greeting and welcoming members and guests, reception, scheduling of

appointments, handling memberships, and answering phone lines. Overseeing the safety of members and guests by providing quality instruction and supervision. General office support including copying, filing, faxing, typing, etc.

## Gold River Racquet Club, 916-638-7001 Customer Service Lead, July 2011 to October 2012

Duties: Greeting members and welcoming guests. Managing the opening and closing procedures for the club, answering of busy phone lines, basic cashier tasks. Entering cash drops, and payroll. Handling member documents and filing paperwork and other office tasks. Giving potential members a tour of the facility, explaining gym equipment and etiquette.

### Education

## **Certificate in Full Stack Web Development**

A 24-week intensive program focused on gaining technical programming skills in HTML5, CSS3, Javascript, JQuery, Bootstrap, Firebase, Node Js, MySQL, MongoDB, Express, Handelbars.js & ReactJS.

## **Certificate in Massage Therapy**

500 hour Massage Therapy certification through Massage Therapy Institute, Davis.